<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Caffeinator</string>
    <item name="caffeineIntakeValue" format="float" type="string">0</item>

    <string name="too_much_caffeine_notification_title">You\'ve consumed too much caffeine!</string>

    <string name="too_much_caffeine_notification_text">Your caffeine amount is %1$s, this is way too high
        and could lead to some undesired health complications like cardiovascular problems in the future. Drink a lot of water, do some light exercise and eat
        fruits with high Vitamin C content.
    </string>

    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_reply">Reply</string>

    <string name="health_advice1_notification_title">Did you know?</string>

    <string name="health_advice1_notification_text">Drinking coffee in the morning is the most
        effective due to lower Adenosine amount in the brain. Consuming Caffeine or Coffee later than 12PM
        already has detrimental effects on your sleep.
        \nDon\'t forget to drink some water with your coffee!
        \nClick me for more information!
    </string>

    <string name="health_advice2_notification_title">Did you know?</string>

    <string name="health_advice2_notification_text">Regularly drinking coffee
        may have health benefits such as reduced risk of illnesses
        like cancer, heart disease , Alzheimer\'s and depression.
        \nDon\'t overdo it with the sugar!
        \nClick me for more information!
    </string>

    <string name="health_advice3_notification_title">How much caffeine is too much caffeine?</string>

    <string name="health_advice3_notification_text">The FDA deems up to 400 mg a day of caffeine as safe for healthy adults.
        Moderate caffeine consumption is associated with numerous health benefits,
        including increased alertness, enhanced physical performance,
        and better cognitive functioning.
        \nClick me for more information!
    </string>

    <string name="health_advice4_notification_title">Did you know?</string>

    <string name="health_advice4_notification_text">Energy drinks contain lower amounts of caffeine
        than your standard cup of coffee. Coffee however, has antioxidative properties that are good for your health,
        but energy drinks contain synthetic caffeine, high amounts of refined sugars, taurine and many other unwanted substances.
        \nClick me for more information!
    </string>

    <string name="health_advice5_notification_title">Did you know?</string>

    <string name="health_advice5_notification_text">It is strongly discouraged to consume caffeine within an hour after eating in order to
        prevent the caffeine from absorbing iron from the consumed food. Previously consumed caffeine in the same day doesn\'t affect your
        diet as long as more than two hours have passed. Ignoring this fact could cause anemia in the future, especially in women.
        \nClick me for more information!
    </string>

    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="graph">Graph</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="Open">open</string>
    <string name="Close">close</string>


</resources>
